[Music]
[Música]
But anyway, let's see, let's see this
Pero bueno vamos a ver a ver vemos este
video if you like from nauter where he talks
vídeo si os parece de nauter donde habla
about the [ __ ] trucks thing that really gets on my
de lo del foll camiones que me toca
nerves, no, not being able to put [ __ ]
mucho las narices no no poder poner en
trucks in the title, man, very
el título del [__] camiones tío muy
good my beloved audience, how are you Kick
buenas mi amado público qué tal Kick
Twitch and viewership, that's what we have on
Twitch y audiencia es lo que tenemos en
the menu today. Let's start, 8,000 viers
el menú de hoy Comencemos 8000 viers
shas, ​​how things have changed around
shas cómo han cambiado las cosas por
here, Twitch is going to [ __ ] and their streams
aquí Twitch va la [__] y su streams
too, okay man, but I've been
también bueno hombre pero llevo 50
live for 50 minutes. I mean, you have to
minutos en directo O sea tienes que
let the people come in, 8,000
dejar que la gente vaya entrando el 8000
viewers, how Twitch is falling. Of course,
viewers cómo está cayendo Twitch Claro
because Choscas had like 20, not like
porque el chocas tenía como 20 no como
20,000, 15,000, well, Choscas, no, no, let's see
20.000 15000 bueno el chocas no no a ver
how much Choscas can
el chocas cuánto puede manejar
normally handle. Last year, I've seen him
normalmente el año pasado yo lo he visto
ain at night when
ain por las noches cuando hemos estado
we've been there and maybe he was there with 10,
nosotros y a lo mejor estaba él con 10
12, 13, well, the audience hasn't dropped that much,
12 13 bueno tampoco ha bajado tanto de
that you have in a live show, you
audiencia que tú tienes en un directo lo
have him more or less at an hour and a half, I
tienes más o menos a la hora y media o
mean, you have to let the people
sea tienes que dejar que la gente vaya
come in.  Twitch I mean but it's
entrando en Twitch o sea pero sí es
true that lately there are less people
cierto que últimamente hay menos gente
on Twitch it's true we're all having
en Twitch es verdad todos estamos
a little less people we already
teniendo un poquito menos de gente ya
know that AC clashes kati expert in
sabemos que choca AC kati experto en
everything specialist in nothing has
todo especialista en nada se ha pasado
never beaten the game Better said I don't stream
el juego nunca Mejor dicho yo no streo
every day because I
cada día porque no me sale de los
simply do not feel like it I have other
[__] simplemente Tengo otras
priorities and my life is not streaming anymore
prioridades y mi vida ya no es streamear
because I've already achieved everything and
porque yo ya lo he conseguido todo y
this is something that you have to get into your
esto es algo que te tienes que meter en
head I'm not a streamer anymore I want to
la cabeza yo ya no soy streamer quiero
be more things than just being a streamer
ser más cosas que que ser streamer
So now I don't stream so many hours
Entonces yo ahora no streo tantas horas
but I stream I keep streaming and like all
pero streame sigo streame and como todos
your favorite streamers I mean yeah look at
tus streamers favoritos O sea si no Mira
the Twitch Tracker for me reducing
el Twitch Tracker que para mí reducir a
my streams by half is streaming what
la mitad mis streamings es streamear lo
your favorite streamers stream
que streaman tus streamers favoritos
because I used to work twice as much as they do it
porque yo trabajaba el doble que ellos
happens that you don't understand that concept
pasa que tú ese concepto no lo entiendes
Because you don't know what it is to sacrifice
Porque no sabes lo que es sacrificarte
or work or discipline you don't know
ni trabajar ni disciplina no lo sabes
but I do know that's why I am where I
pero yo sí lo sé por eso estoy donde
am I mean I recommend you look at
estoy O sea que te recomiendo que mires
the Twitch Tracker and look at the hours that
el Twitch Tracker y mires las horas que
all the other top streamers stream
streaman todos los demás streamers del
And so you'll see that I have simply
top Y así pues verás que yo simplemente
reduced my  my work day in
he hecho reducir mi mi jornada laboral a
half which is what is mentally healthy what are
la mitad que es lo sano mentalmente que
they doing for what the [ __ ]
es lo que hacen ellos para que hostias
is that he says I have reduced my
es que dice he reducido mi jornada
work day I saw this Today on the
laboral esto lo he visto Yo hoy en el
news I think it was on the news Yes in the
noti creo que ha sido en el not Sí en el
newscast he reduced his work day
noticiero ha reducido su jornada laboral
to doing 7 or 8 hours of Streaming, I mean
a hacer 7 8 horas de Stream o sea
How many [ __ ] hours was there man 7 or 8 hours
Cuántas [__] horas haía tío 7 8 horas
of Streaming in a row, I mean because in
de Stream seguido o sea porque yo en
reality if I start adding up all the
realidad si me pongo a sumar todas las
hours that I am working Al Día it is
horas que estoy trabajando Al Día son
more evident because I record news
más evidentemente porque yo grabo noti
both for telesalseo and salsería
tanto de telesalseo como de salsería
Let's say it's an hour more or less ok
Ponle que es una hora más o menos vale
an hour of recording let's say half an hour
una hora de grabación ponle media hora
reviewing the script each one compiling
revisando el guion cada uno recopilando
news and all that stuff Let's say 3
noticias y todo el rollo ese Ponle que 3
hours and a bit I am working on the
horas y pico estoy trabajando en los
newscasts okay live I normally
noticieros vale en directos normalmente
do two one in the salsería and another between
hago dos uno en la salsería y otro entes
salsería if there are topics if there are no topics then it's
salseo si hay temas si no hay temas pues
not worth live it's 4 or 5 hours between those
no vale directo son 4 o 5 horas entre
that you spend live and between those that
las que pasas en directo y entre la que
you collect a little no And you prepare a little
recopilas un poco no Y preparas un poco
the live no eh And yes I can record video
el directo no eh Y si Puedo grabar vídeo
the  main because there is it is recorded if not
el principal porque haya se graba si no
neither or I mean but in total it is [ __ ]
tampoco o sea pero en total es [__]
crazy but whether you like it or not it is not
locura pero quieras que no no está
always yes really yes really yes it is [ __ ]
siempre sí en verdad sí en verdad sí es
crazy me When when
una [__] locura yo Cuando cuando pase
a year passes and I farm a lot lose weight And I will
uno años y farme mucho rebajar Y
surely end up doing something more
seguramente acabaré haciendo algo más
calm or every day maybe one
tranqui o bien cada día a lo mejor una
thing imagine one day a live on
cosa imagínate un día un directo en
salsería another day a live on t salseo
salsería otro día un directo en t salseo
another day a video from the main Channel
otro día un vídeo del Canal principal
every day one thing Pin Pin Pin but not
cada día una cosa Pin Pin Pin pero no
everything every day not everything every
todo todos los días no todo todos los
day surely but we'll see maybe
días seguramente pero ya veremos a lo
in 4 years imagine that
mejor de aquí a 4 años imagínate que
I have more work still I recommend
tengo más trabajo todavía te recomiendo
that you take a look and that you shut up
que le eches un vistazo y que te calles
more often when you don't know what you
más menudo cuando no sabes de lo que
're talking about but Likewise, he had
estás hablando pero Igualmente ha tenido
the detail to talk or analyze the issue
el detalle de hablar o analizar el tema
of the drop in audience or viewers
de bajada de audiencia o espectadores
for example today by had almost
por ejemplo hoy by ha tenido casi
100,000 people in a msi tiwan with
100,000 personas en un msi tiwan con
traj 2 at 2 in the afternoon that 2
traj 2 a las 2 de la tarde eso hace 2
years ago would have had 200,000 people yes it
años hubiese tenido 200,000 personas sí
is true I mean it is a lot of people have
es cierto o sea es mucha gente han
dropped so much dude
bajado tantísimo tío los usuarios de
Twitch users it's true there would have been a lot
Twitch es cierto hubiese habido mucha
more but well it is what it is I mean
más pero bueno es lo que hay o sea
inevitably everything has gone
inevitablemente ha bajado todo un poco y
down a bit and that's it but [ __ ] having 8000 people in 50 minutes is very good because we're here quietly talking about LOL it's fine I mean it's not that many people but yes we've all gone down a bit it's normal Nothing happens coo but for example in this in these last few weeks
ejemplo en esto en estas últimas semanas
here for example I have noticed less
aquí por ejemplo sí que he notado menos
audience in general us let's see
audiencia en general nosotros a ver
us the channels we depend a
nosotros los canales de se dependemos un
bit on the topics that are there How many
poco de la de los temas que haya Cuántos
viewers does uncle shur usually have
espectadores suele tener el tío shur en
live How many viewers does
directo Cuántos espectadores suele tener
uncle shur usually have live these days how many
tío shur en directo estos días cuántos
viewers does he have 2000 viewers did
espectadores tiene 2000 espectadores
uncle Sur have today and today eh A day
tenía el tío Sur hoy y s hoy eh Un día
like today or yesterday because it's Sunday Ah
como hoy o ayer porque que es domingo Ah
no 2000 on average Ah that is in ki
no 2000 de media Ah que está en ki
then it will be less clear No but if it came
entonces tendrá menos claro No pero si a
out to me here that I was
mí me ha salido aquí que estaba en
live a while ago I mean we
directo hace un rato O sea nosotros
depend a lot on the topics but yes it's
dependemos mucho de los temas pero sí
true that these last few weeks I have
que verdad que estas últimas semanas he
noticed fewer viewers here but it's
notado yo menos espectadores aquí pero
also costing us  life
es que también nos está costando la vida
to us rcat topics eh of gossip this
a nosotros rcat temas eh de salseos esta
week eh about Kill I have to
semana eh lo de Kill le tengo que
ask Uncle Sur cell always has
preguntar al tío Sur cel siempre tiene
200 300 about Kill I have to
200 300 lo de Kill le tengo que
ask Uncle Sur why is he
preguntar al tío Sur Por qué está
doing that and also I'm opening very
haciendo eso y además estoy abriendo muy
early it's 4 in the afternoon not 8 in
pronto son las 4 de la tarde no las 8 de
the afternoon it's normal we're going to play a
la tarde es normal vamos a jugar juego
vampire game which is not a very
de vampiros que tampoco es un juego muy
fashionable game it's okay nothing happens it's a
moda está bien no pasa nada es un una
good one Yeah we who are streaming and
buen Sí nosotros que estamos streame and
very late too eh You'll see the people
muy tarde también eh Ya verás la gente
who are going to watch it in the eh in Wow
que va a ver en el en el eh en el Wow
when Cataclysm comes out there will be
cuando salca cataclisma ahí sí que va a
few people there I'll be surprised the
haber poca gente ahí me sorprenderá el
day we pass 100,000 viewers
día que pasem por los 100,000 viewers
But hey nothing happens damn you have to
Pero bueno no pasa nada [__] hay que
enjoy life a little sometimes there are
disfrutar un poco de la vida a veces hay
more people sometimes there are less and when I
más gente a veces hay menos y cuando
'm playing Belum then talk to more than
esté jugando belum pues hablá más de
100,000 people most days of
100,000 personas la mayoría de los días
course it's a series of rast such with
claro es una serie de rast tal con
friends there will be a lot of famous people Loy
amigos va a haber mucha gente famosa Loy
Nothing happens [ __ ] it's okay I mean
No pasa nada [__] está bien o sea
think I mean  that Twitch goes in cycles and
piensa O sea que Twitch va por ciclos y
streamers too but for me it's going
los streamers también pero a mí me va
very well on kiik it's having an average
muy e en kiik sí está teniendo una media
of 600-700 viewers uncle Sur Yeah
de 600 700 espectadores el tío Sur Sí
sure but on ki they have less of course it's that
claro pero en en ki tienen menos claro
on ki that's not good man I still stay
es que en ki que no bien tío yo me sigo
very high estimating much
manteniendo muy arriba estimando mucho
less it's fine We've all gone down a
menos está bien Todos hemos bajado un
bit and it's fine it's okay we've all
poco y está bien no pasa nada todos lo
done it Juanito Generally in a
hemos hecho Juanito Generalmente en una
Minecraft series I would have 45,000
serie de Minecraft tendría 45,000
people and now how many do you have How many is
personas y ahora Cuántas tienes Cuántas
your baller I don't know because I'm not
tu baller No lo sé porque no estoy en
live but chur says he's earning
directo pero chur dice que está ganando
three times more for fewer subscribers seriously
tres veces más por menos subs en serio
man seriously man But well if you
tío en serio tío Pero bueno si si tú
do a live on kiik and nobody donates to you
haces un directo en kiik y nadie te dona
for example here in this
por ejemplo nosotros aquí en este
live we have in this live we have
directo tenemos en este directo nosotros
had today for example
que hemos tenido hoy por ejemplo
we in this live we have had
nosotros en este directo hemos tenido
some super chat okay that they add up to $ and
algunos super chat vale de que suman $ y
11 members and if they don't donate
11 miembros y si no te donan
absolutely anything to you what At least
absolutamente nada qué Por lo menos
YouTube earns the monetization no and if it
YouTube ganas la monetización no y s que
has gone up I can't imagine that about 30,000
ha subido no me imagino que unas 30.000
is a kiss  stev Thanks a lot handsome
es un beso stev Muchas gracias guapo
nothing to thank you much but of course a
nada que agradecer mucho pero claro es
year ago a year and a half Juanito
que hace un año un año y medio Juanito
playing that instead of 30,000 he would have
jugando a eso en vez de 30,000 tendría
45,000 which is 50% more audience of course it
45,000 es un 50% más de audiencia claro
seems like little but it's a lot You know, I
es que parece poco pero es mucho Sabes o
mean there's a very big difference,
sea es que hay una diferencia muy grande
Twitch has gone down Of course it has gone down
ha bajado Twitch Claro que ha bajado
Look at the general statistics We have all
Mirad las estadísticas generales Todos
gone down a little bit, oh well it's okay
hemos bajado poco tal buo está bien no
nothing's wrong damn It's still very good
pasa nada [__] Sigue estando muy bien
coo I don't watch Twitch I don't see it as
coo yo Twitch no lo veo para no lo veo
a platform that's going to be around
una plataforma que se vaya a quedar toda
forever I don't see Twitch as a
la vida yo Twitch no lo veo una
platform That's why then Upload the
plataforma Por eso luego Sube los
extracts to YouTube now but I upload the
extractos a YouTube ya pero yo subo los
extracts and also the entire live shows there
extractos y también los directos enteros
are people who watch the entire live shows eh
hay gente que ve los directos enteros eh
a lot of people watch the entire live shows
mucha gente ve los directos enteros
we've had a lot of people we
hemos tenido mucha gente seguimos
can still experience this the majority is that it's not
pudiendo vivir esto la mayoría es que no
just that they watch the entire live shows there
solamente es que vean los directos
are a lot of people Uh
enteros es que hay mucha gente Eh que de
suddenly let's see if I can give you an
repente a ver si os puedo poner algún
example wait man they are like videos the
ejemplo espera tío son como vídeos los
live shows once they end they are videos
directos una vez que terminan son vídeos
okay And are they recommended or not as videos  And
vale Y se recomiendan o no como vídeos Y
then suddenly
entonces de repente
MMM mm imagine let's see if I find there was
MMM mm imagínate a ver si encuentro hubo
a live stream recently this guy wait
un directo hace poco este tío espérate
I'm going to put the statistics and share it with you
voy a poner la estadística y os lo
okay This live stream the other day
comparto vale Este directo el otro día
okay This live stream the other day well the other
vale Este directo el otro día bueno el
day
otro día no
I don't know last month or the other one I don't
e yo que sé el mes pasado o el otro no
remember when it was okay Suddenly I
me acuerdo Cuándo fue vale De repente me
see this live stream in the statistics
veo este directo en las estadísticas
you know like the most viewed video of
sabes como el vídeo más visto de de de
the salsería of the month and it was that suddenly
la salsería del mes y era que de repente
this live stream called now let's see
este directo que se llama ahora vemos
What is it okay suddenly it had been
Cuál es vale de repente se había se ha
shared and it reached
compartido y ha llegado a
125,000 views okay suddenly I don't know if you
125,000 visitas vale de repente no sé si
can see the date here I
aquí se puede ver la fecha a mí que me
like them more on mobile the truth is I
gustan más en el móvil la verdad me
like them more on mobile okay I like them
gustan más en el móvil vale me gustan
more on mobile because I don't know why I
más en el móvil porque no sé por qué lo
find it more intuitive But well uh
veo más intuitivo Pero bueno eh fue muy
that live stream was very good what live stream is it a store let's
bueno ese directo qué directo es tienda
see the monkey this monkey if he was born in
a ver el mono este mono si ha nacido en
Peru he is Peruvian This was Well I don't know
Perú es peruano Esto fue Pues no lo sé
here I am answering this kid who
aquí estoy contestando al niño este que
messed with me Agustín okay Here
se metió conmigo al Agustín vale Aquí
is this little girl that I don't remember what
está esta chiquilla que no me acuerdo
happened to her then she had
que es lo que le pasaba luego tenía
also the Abi thing I don't remember
también la movida Abi no me acuerdo
because that's what it was it was more or less around
porque es lo que fue fue fue más o menos
these times of Look February of
los tiempos estos de Mira febrero del
last year when there was this thing that if
año pasado que estaba el rollo de que si
fuab a vi that s Look Ah look [ __ ] yeah
fuab a vi que s Mira Ah mira [__] si
look it's the live where carche is
mira es el directo donde carche se está
eating the hamburger thing or rather
comiendo lo de la hamburguesa o sea
look t okay we also react to
fíjate t vale también reaccionamos a
some utbh around here but come on it's what I'm
algo de utbh por aquí pero vamos es lo
telling you I mean m I prefer to do them
que te digo o sea m yo prefiero hacerlos
on YouTube because I know that they've uploaded
en YouTube porque sé que han subidos ahí
videos there man and maybe they're videos
son vídeos tío y a lo mejor son vídeos
that then [ __ ] suddenly catch on after
que luego [__] de repente cogen luego
almost two months the number of views shot up
de casi dos meses se disparó de visita
yeah yeah yeah yeah months went by and suddenly
sí sí sí sí pasaron meses y de repente
for whatever reason ytube
pues por lo que sea se posicionó ytube
YouTube was positioned like that and suddenly boom and [ __ ] Well maybe all
YouTube así y de repente pum y [__] Pues
of a sudden you've earned what can
a lo mejor de repente has ganado qué te
I tell you a few hundred euros
digo yo unos cuantos de cientos de euros
eh For a video that you already made two
eh Por un vídeo que ya hiciste hace dos
or three months ago that's why I'm not
o tres meses por eso a mí no me preocupa
too worried eh And it's the philosophy sorry about the
mucho eh Y es la es la filosofía perdón
content that I'm making on the
de contenido que estoy haciendo en el
main channel which are timeless videos Eh
canal principal que son vídeos Eh
worth more than more than gossip
atemporales vale más que más que salseo
yes I keep trying to gossip here  in in
sí que sigo tratando salseo aquí en en
the salseria not this everyday salseo
la salsería no el salseo este de todos
of youtuber this the other no and
los días de youtuber esto lo otro no y
in telesalseo of the heart but removing
en telesalseo del corazón pero quitando
Maybe a video like this you know that is
A lo mejor un vídeo así sabes que sea
more I don't know one more controversy that is worth
más no sé una polémica más que merezca
being chosen for the main one
la pena ser elegida para el principal
are more timeless topics what is worth eh
son temas más atemporales lo que vale eh
the Asunta case Well now it is
el caso asunta Bueno pues ahora está
hitting hard but it is a case that has been going on for
pegando fuerte pero es un caso que hace
11 years and every so often it
ya 11 años y cada cierto tiempo se
goes viral again either because a documentary comes out
vuelve a viralizar o bien porque sale un
or because it releases a series
documental o porque saca una serie
because whatever is worth it There already has
porque lo que sea vale Ahí ya lleva
62,000 views okay This was it look at you
62,000 visitas vale Esto fue fíjate tú
This was a video that I uploaded To upload the
Esto fue un vídeo que subí Por subir el
other day because I hadn't had time
otro día porque no me había dado tiempo
to record the Mexican damer that this one
de grabar el del damer mexicano que este
hasn't gotten many views but it will
no me ha cogido muchas visitas pero
surely get them with time okay
seguro que las cogerá con el tiempo vale
Why Well because in the Mexican damer case there are
Por qué Pues porque del caso del damer
many things missing suddenly
mexicano faltan muchas cosas de repente
the trial is still missing more
falta todavía el juicio más
investigation will already be carried out okay
investigación ya se vir realizará vale
eh what can I tell you, I mean in 200,000 views
eh qué te digo o sea em 200,000 visitas
I got This video and this is going to be a
me cogido Este vídeo y este va a ser un
video that is not going  never to die eh that one from
vídeo que no va a morir nunca eh ese de
Fran You realize that the case of
Fran Tú date cuenta que el caso de
Daniel Sancho has been now How many years will the
Daniel Sancho ha sido ahora Cuántos años
Daniel Sancho case be talked about if
se va a hablar del caso Daniel Sancho si
today they still talk about the
a día de hoy todavía se habla del caso
Asunta case or the Marta Castillo case, the
asunta o del caso Marta castillo del
case I don't know what Or the case, I mean the subject
caso no sé qué O del caso o sea el tema
of cases are so timeless you know
de los casos son tan atemporales sabes
the documentary that I made man, I mean, wow,
el documental que hice tío o sea vaya
almost 300,000 views, an
por casi 300,000 visitas un vídeo de una
hour and a half video, I mean this This has
hora y media o sea esto Esto me ha
generated an incredible amount of money, an
generado un un dineral increíble pero un
incredible amount of money aarte is that I have
dineral increíble aarte es que yo tengo
a huge amount of SPM so these are topics that I
un pedazo de spm entonces son temas que
choose okay this one this one does
los voy eligiendo vale este este sí que
surprise me a lot that it only failed at
me extraña mucho que haya pinchado a tan
22,000 but oh well it's what I'm telling you, I'm
solo 22000 pero bueno es lo que os digo
not worried because it's a fight from
no me preocupa porque es una pelea de
many years ago, maybe
hace muchos años lo mismo de repente el
next year you'll remind me and we'll see it
año que viene me lo recordáis y lo vemos
and maybe it will have 150,000 like what happens
y a lo mejor tiene 150.000 como le pasa
with that live one okay I mean these are topics that are a
a ese directo vale o sea son temas un
little more timeless okay
poco más atemporales vale contenido con
higher quality content higher quality content and
más calidad contenido con más calidad y
then the series man the series man that we
luego la serie tío la serie tío que
start  100,000 views each episode
empezamos 100.000 visitas cada episodio
and there are some chapters that already have
y hay algunos capítulos que tienen ya
almost 200,000 views Look at this you know and
casi 200,000 visitas Mira este sabes y
it's the move we're doing now
es la movida que estamos haciendo ahora
in the main okay Okay man
en el principal vale Está bien hombre no
nothing happens up and down nothing happens then
pasa nada sub y baja pasa nada entonces
choquita we had to wait for
choquita había que esperar a que la
people to appear I mean you have to let
gente apareciera O sea tienes que dejar
people enter Twitch bad
que la gente vaya entrando en Twitch mal
time bad time and also I'm
horario mala hora y además estoy
opening very early it's 4 in the
abriendo muy pronto son las 4 de la
afternoon not 8 in the afternoon or are we talking about a
tarde no las 8 de la tarde o hablamos de
generic term I say this because
término genérico lo digo porque
anyone would say that you're
cualquiera diría que te estás
justifying yourself with your
justificando con tus estadísticas
particular statistics IV today you really
particulares IV mismo hoy tú de verdad
believe that IB would have had 100k
crees que IB hubiese tenido 100k de
viewers Peak of 100k viewers
viewers Pico de 100k de viewers
only in a G2 against tiwan del MC at
solamente en un G2 contra tiwan del MC a
2 in the afternoon fifth map that type
las 2 de la tarde quinto mapa ese tipo
of income will maintain your income
de ingreso te mantendrán los ingresos
without working in the future well let's see it's not
sin trabajar a futuro bueno a ver no es
that we are auron Play or anything like that
que seamos auron Play ni nada de eso
but suddenly I can take
pero de repente sí que me puedo tomar
more liberties see I don't know if
más libertades ver yo no sé si las
Joe Hunter's statistics Look at
estadísticas de Joe Hunter Mira las
Joe's statistics are very good
estadísticas de Joe están muy bien
because it tells you maybe How many
porque te dice a lo mejor Cuántas
visits They do not belong  a al último mes bien
visitas No pertenecen a al último mes
imaginar eh Javi oliveira Javi
vale imagínate eh Javi oliveira Javi
oliveira has 6 million visits from
oliveira tiene 6 millones de visitas de
previous periods, that is, of the 13
periodos anteriores o sea de los 13
million visits that he had
millones de visitas que tuvo el mes
last month, 6 million are from other months
pasado 6 millones son de de otros meses
of videos that were already uploaded, yes, it
de vídeos que ya estaban subidos que sí
is true that many visits are from
que es verdad que muchas visitas son de
shorts, but many are not, eh Let's say that
short pero muchas no eh Ponle que la
half are not worth it, la salsería and telesalseo,
mitad no vale la salsería y telesalseo
okay, look at these two, la salsería and
vale mira estos dos la salsería Y
telesalseo, well, la salsería and telesalseo,
telesalseo pues la salsería y telesalseo
what are these two previous periods?
qué son estos dos periodos anteriores
These two, two are not. Up this one and this one that
estos dos dos no Arriba este y este que
doesn't appear I don't know why. How strange, mm,
no sale No sé por qué Qué raro mm
telesalseo, little 200,000 and this one, I don't know
telesalseo poco 200,000 y este no sé por
why, it didn't register it. Maybe
qué no lo no lo registró A lo mejor
because I deleted a video, which also happens
porque borré vídeo que también pasa eso
when I delete a video. Eh, there are many
cuando borro vídeo Eh hay hay muchos
months, maybe if there are many,
meses a lo mejor que si son muchas
many, many millions of visits from
muchas muchos millones de visitas de
other months, okay, people, that was a year ago,
otros meses valea gente eso hace un año
a year and a half ago, it would have had,
un año y medio hubiese tenido es que ni
you can't even imagine 150, 200,000 at least.
te lo imaginas 150 200,000 como mínimo
But well, over time, yes, over
Pero bueno con el tiempo sí con el
time, that's what  I tell you, I mean it's
tiempo sí es lo que os digo o sea es un
something that I want to achieve, you
es algo que quiero llegar a alcanzar me
understand, stay maybe with the
entiendes quedarme a lo mejor con la
peace of mind of doing less things
tranquilidad de ir haciendo menos cosas
but that I have some income there for at
pero que tenga ahí unos ingresos para
least, or rather a crazy amount of people to
como mínimo o sea una locura de gente a
your secret channel, how is it going? Well, that
tu canal secreto cómo le va pues ese
secret channel, the truth is that it has dropped a
canal secreto la verdad es que ha bajado
lot, we are trying to fix it,
mucho lo estamos intentando arreglar
but it has dropped a lot, a lot, a lot of the
Pero ha bajado mucho pero mucho mucho
level, eh, a lot, a lot of the level that maybe it is
nivel eh mucho mucho nivel que a lo
giving 300 bucks a month when it was
mejor está dando 300 pavos al mes cuando
giving much more than 10 times that would have
daba mucho más que 10 veces eso hubiese
had a lot more fifth map tiw
tenido muchísima más quinto mapa tiw
against G2, damn historic, let's go, there are few
contra G2 [__] histórico vamos es poca
people for what it could be for what it
gente para lo que podría ser para lo que
could be, yes, it is true, I mean, it is a
podría ser si que es cierto o sea es una
validity, man, but if everything goes down
es una validad hombre pero si todo Baja
a little, well, it's okay, man, there is
un poco s bueno no pasa nada hombre hay
no need to go crazy with that, then
no hay que volverse loco con eso luego
he debates the theory with something that he
le debate la teoría con algo que a él
loves so much with the numbers, c, he
tanto le encanta con los numeritos c
had 200 can and nobody expected this, my
tenía 200 can y esto nadie lo esperaba
people, it's time to take out the expert card,
mi gente toca sacar la carta del experto
okay, but he would have had much more time, what
vale pero tendría mucho más ha tiempo lo
happens is that many of you see
que pasa es que muchos de vosotros veis
a big number and think that everything is going
un número grande y pensáis que todo va
well and it couldn't be much better, the
bien y no podría ir mucho mejor el
problem is that  you understand the
problema es que no entendéis de las
proportions I'm not saying to promise
proporciones no digo prometerme con
you but understand me I am a
vosotros pero entenderme Yo soy una
person specialized in this and I know how
persona especializada en esto y sé cómo
audiences work, I mean what I
funcionan las audiencias o sea lo que yo
tell you in this in these topics man I'm
os digo en este en estos temas tío yo lo
very sorry but it's mass I mean
siento mucho pero va misa es decir
when you're watching 200k if you get to
cuando tú estás viendo 200k si lo llegas
see it in the middle of a pandemic that would have
a ver en plena pandemia ese tendría
half a million for you is it an idea
medio millón para que te ha es una idea
or 350 400,000 yes it is true that in the
o 350 400,000 sí que es verdad que en la
time of the pandemic we were
época de la pandemia como que triunfamos
very successful No what happens is that you don't
mucho No lo que pasa es que tú no no
know how twit works but I do
conoces cómo funciona twit pero yo sí
[ __ ] because I was crazy about
[__] porque yo era un loco de las
statistics now I don't see them as much
estadísticas ahora ya no las veo tanto
but I understand the market ent what
pero entiendo el mercado ent lo que a ti
seems big to you and it seems very big what
te parece grande y parece muy grande que
Fabricio says 10 times 300 That's 30,000 a
dice Fabricio 10 veces 300 Son 30.000 al
month watch out Javi high figures and you have
mes ojo Javi cifras altas y tú tienes ag
people from the Treasury watching your live shows be
gente de Hacienda viendo tus directos
careful Javi I ask you Fabricio if I
cuidado Javi te lo pido Fabricio si yo
earned 30,000 30,000 on one of the
cobrara 30.000 30.000 en uno de los
channels okay Eh well the Treasury  I would know
canales vale Eh pues Hacienda lo sabría
no and I wouldn't hide it I wouldn't hide it it doesn't
no y no lo ocultaría no lo ocultaría no
matter you understand but the thing is
importa me entiendes pero lo que pasa es
that 10 times 300 is not 30,000 King
que 10 veces 300 no son 30.000 Rey
Juanito has 30k but he's very good he's the
Juanito tenga 30k pero muy bien es la
best but of course a year and a
[__] pero claro es que hace un año y
half ago he would have had much more
medio hubiese tenido mucho más por
because the audience has dropped little by
porque la audiencia ha bajado poco a
little you can see it in the statistics
poco lo puedes ver en las estadísticas
everyone in general we have had
tod todos en general hemos tenido meses
good months we have had bad months but
buenos hemos tenido meses malos pero en
overall there are a little fewer people
overall hay un poquito menos de gente
for the last couple of months two three
desde hace un par de meses dos tres
months and for years it has been dropping
meses y desde hace años ha ido bajando
due to the pandemic I don't know about you my people
de la pandemia yo no sé ustedes mi gente
but I'm left with this clip what I
pero yo me quedo con este clip lo que yo
really say on these issues guys I'm
digo de verdad en en estos temas tíos yo
very sorry but my
lo siento mucho pero va mis
intransigence goes I invoke you and the little
intransigencia yo te invoco y el
detail of me before with the
detallito de yo antes con las
statistics bu what a sick man I was
estadísticas bu menudo enfermo yo era un
crazy about statistics now I don't
loco de las estadísticas ahora ya no las
see them as much but I understand the market now it's
veo tanto pero entiendo el mercado ahora
no longer worth it is aware of everything that is
ya no vale está al tanto de todo lo que
happening but now not this month has
está pasando pero ahora no este mes ha
been the worst month in history May 2024
sido el peor mes histórico mayo de 2024
has been the worst month in history since Mira
ha sido el peor mes histórico desde Mira
2 280  Look, since November December
2 280 Mira desde noviembre diciembre de
2020 pre-pandemic and what this leads to,
2020 prepandemia y en qué desemboca esto
well, on kik my people are affecting the
pues en kik mi gente está afectando la
green platform to
plataforma verde a las estadísticas de
Twitch statistics, it is also true that Kick may have
Twitch también es cierto que Kick puede
affected Yes, yes, it may have
haber afectado Sí sí puede haber
affected How many thousands of viewers does ki have
afectado Cuántos miles de viewers tiene
now, people like wescol, for example?
ahora ki gente como wescol por ejemplo
How many viewers did he bring to Twitch, well,
Cuántos viewers traía a Twitch pues
many, tens of thousands, tens
muchos muchos decenas de miles decenas
of thousands, people like him, well, he has taken
de miles gente como él pues ha quitado
viewers from Twitch, man, obviously yes,
viers a Twitch hombre evidentemente sí
obviously Yes, how many
evidentemente Sí cuántos streamers
Latin streamers and especially Argentinian streamers, how many
latinos y sobre todo argentinos cuánta
people from Argentina have gone here, a
gente de Argentina se ha ido aquí un
lot? I don't know, I had said that the
montón No sé unal I había dicho que las
statistics are manipulated there.
estadísticas las manipulan por allí
Let's go people, I'll tell you one thing, if
Vámonos a gente yo os digo una cosa si
we do the evening on Kick, yes, it will be
hacemos la velada en Kick eso sí que se
Busted by four apart from the fact that he will put on you what
Peta por cuatro aparte de que te pond
comes out of his balls er when
los que le sale de los huevos er cuando
we all find out that I am 13
todos nos enteramos que I tiene 13
years old and the 50k Bot s Yes, all of you
añitos y el 50k de Bot s Sí todos los
who say that W has Bots
que decí que W tiene Bots en todas
everywhere, I suppose you are 13 years old.
partes Yo supongo que tendréis 13 años
Thank you very much, Isuka,
Muchísimas gracias isuka
gorgeous to Body
guapísima to Body
queen  Oh
reina Oh
[Music]
[Música]